

PROFILE -

Energetic software developer with 1+ years of experience developing robust code for high-volume businesses. Areas of interest are Machine Learning, Natural Language Processing, Artificial Intelligence and Soft Computing.

Currently working as a Software Developer at LCEPL PVT. LTD.

PUBLICATIONS —

International: 2

National: 1

PERSONAL —

D.O.B LANGUAGES 26 FEB 1990

LANGUAGESENG|HIN|MAR|URDUHOBBIESFOOTBALL|HALAMADRID

CONTACT -



+91 8149448939 +91 8329587191



asrar60@gmail.com asrar2602@outlook.com



Amravati, Maharashtra India- 444601

SOCIAL MEDIA -



linkedin.com/in/asrar-ahmad-4a2b4a64



facbook.com/asrar786



github.com/asrar2602



twitter.com/Asrar2602

ASRAR AHMAD

Software Developer

LCEPL PVT. LTD.

Web Profile: - https://asrar2602.github.io

EXPERIENCE

May 2017-June 2018

Expert WebSoft Pvt. Ltd

Junior Software Developer

- Analyze users' needs
- Designing and coding
- Design each piece of the application and plan how the pieces will work together

2015- 2017

SGB Amravati University

Visiting Assistant Professor

- Teaching theory and practical in the Post Graduate Department of Computer Science & Engineering
- It includes Data Mining, Machine Learning and Soft Computing

EDUCATION

2012-2015

M.E in Computer Science & IT

- Major in Data Science and Machine Learning
- CGPA: 8.11

2007-2011

B.E in Computer Science & Engineering

- Major in Machine Learning and Pattern Recognition
- Percent: 67.78 %

2006-2007

Higher Secondary School (HSC)

- Maharashtra State Board
- Percent: 83.83

2005-2006

Secondary School (SSC)

- Maharashtra State Board
 - Percent: 79.46 %

SKILLS

Java JQuery JavaScript
AngularJS NodeJS HTML/CSS